(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
公演ハッシュタグ #ひろがるホロライブDAY2
Performance Hashtag: #ひろがるホロライブDAY2
開演までよろしくお楽しみに
Please look forward to the start of the performance.
SNSでの感想投稿OK！スクリーンショット大歓迎！
Posting impressions on SNS is OK! Screenshots are welcome!
録音・録画・ミラー配信は固く禁止いたします
Recording, filming, and mirror streaming are strictly prohibited.
グッズラインナップ紹介
オンライン通販も開始！
Merchandise Lineup Introduction
Online sales have also started!
OFFICIAL ITEMS
Tシャツ White / Black
T-Shirt White / Black
ペンライト / マフラータオル
Penlight / Muffler Towel
PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
EXPO & 4th fes 楽しみ！！
Looking forward to EXPO & 4th fes!!
I love my hololive wife: Marine Senchou
メルちゃん お疲れ様！！
Mel-chan, good job!!
スバルちゃん大好き！！
I love Subaru-chan!!
ライブ最高！！
The live was awesome!!
みこちー！！ 35Pより
Miko-chi!! From 35P
ねねち LOVE
Nene-chi LOVE
ホロライブに感謝！！
Thanks to hololive!!
フブキ最高！！
Fubuki is the best!!
マリン船長大好き！！
I love Captain Marine!!
応援してます！！
I'm supporting you!!
ホロライブ 4th fes 最高！！
hololive 4th fes is the best!!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023
グッズラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
オンライン通販も開始！
Online sales have also started!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production members are gathering on cards once again!
ひろがるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiss Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack: hololive production Vol.2
3月24日(金)発売
Releasing on Friday, March 24th
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ブースターパック 3月24日(金)発売
Booster Pack On Sale March 24th (Fri)
Our Bright Parade × JOYSOUND
スペシャルコラボレーション
Special Collaboration
2023年5月28日(日)まで
全国の対象カラオケ店で実施中！
Running until May 28, 2023 (Sun)
at participating karaoke stores nationwide!
コラボドリンクをご注文の方に、
オリジナルコースタープレゼント！
Order a collab drink and get
an original coaster as a gift!
過去ライブの配信など他にも企画が盛りだくさん！
詳しくは みるハコ
Tons of other projects like past live streams!
Search 'Miru Hako' for details
Hype light drive bypass my vital
Locked in a loop to a better life
だって全開やっちゃって
もうやめてみたい
Because I'm going full throttle,
I want to try stopping now
どうしちゃったの
絶対絶対絶対好きでしょ
What's wrong?
You definitely, definitely, definitely like it, right?
Are you appetite now?
I'm pushing somehow
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023
グッズ ラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロスターズ / ホロスターズ EN
HOLOSTARS / HOLOSTARS English
hololive production Art Collection
ホロライブ 事務所グッズ
hololive Office Goods
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
ブシロード グッズ
Bushiroad Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
OFFICIAL ITEMS
Our Bright Parade
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
デジタルメッセージボード
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
Digital Message Board
デジタルメッセージボード
Originals / Covers
グッズラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロスターズ グッズ
Holostars Goods
hololive production Art Collection / B2タペストリー
hololive production Art Collection / B2 Tapestry
ホロライブ事務所グッズ
Hololive Office Goods
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
BUSHIROAD グッズ
BUSHIROAD Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
OFFICIAL ITEMS
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
DIGITAL MESSAGE BOARD
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiβ Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production members are gathering in cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiβ Schwarz!
ブースターパック...
Booster pack...
ホロライブプロダクション ボリューム2
Hololive Production Volume 2
ブシロード
Bushiroad
Our Bright Parade x JOYSOUND
スペシャルコラボレーション
Special Collaboration
ハイライトのバイバイバイバイバイ 丸めてポイ...
Highlight's bye-bye-bye-bye-bye, roll it up and toss...
だって全然やんなくなっちゃって もうやめていたい
Because I've stopped doing it completely, I want to quit already
どうしちゃったの 絶対絶対絶対好きでいて
What happened? Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely keep loving me
Are you embarrassed right now or blushing somehow
響き合うメロディ 手を繋いでパレード
Melodies resonating, holding hands in a parade
一歩ずつ踏みしめて 夢が叶う場所へ
Taking it step by step, to the place where dreams come true
独りきりじゃないから...
Because you're not alone...
...虹の橋を架けてゆこう
...let's build a bridge of rainbows
グッズラインナップ紹介
Merchandise Lineup Introduction
オンライン通販も開始！
Online sales have also started!
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロスターズ 商品ラインナップ！
HOLOSTARS Product Lineup!
空を突き抜けてゆこう
Let's go, breaking through the sky
最高の笑顔で
With our best smiles
hololive production Art Collection
響き合うメロディ
Melodies resonating
手を繋いでパレード
Holding hands in a parade
一歩ずつ踏みしめて
Taking it step by step
夢が叶う場所へ
To the place where dreams come true
独りきりじゃないから...
Because you're not alone...
ホロライブ 事務所グッズ
hololive Production Office Goods
...虹の橋を架けてゆこう
...let's build a bridge of rainbows
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo＊27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
商品ラインナップ！
holo*27 コラボグッズ
Product Lineup!
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
BUSHIROAD グッズ
BUSHIROAD Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
OFFICIAL ITEMS
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
グッズラインナップ紹介
Merchandise Lineup Introduction
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロライブ事務所グッズ
Hololive Office Goods
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
ホロライブ × MANGART BEAMS コラボグッズ
Hololive x MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
MANGART BEAMS コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
BUSHIROAD グッズ
BUSHIROAD Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
OFFICIAL ITEMS
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiβ Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is gathering on cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiβ Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2、3月24日(金)発売！
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol.2, on sale Friday, March 24th!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
JOYSOUND スペシャルコラボレーション
JOYSOUND Special Collaboration
コラボドリンクをご注文の方に、オリジナルコースタープレゼント！
Order a collab drink to get an original coaster!
詳しくは みるハコ
Check Miruhaco for more details!
holo*27 NOW ON SALE
盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get hyped!
ふーちゃん
Fuu-chan
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
ふーちゃん フレア推し
Fuu-chan Flare Fan
ときのそら
Tokino Sora
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
夜空メル
Yozora Mel
紫咲シオン
Murasaki Shion
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
癒月ちょこ
Yuzuki Choco
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
天音かなた
Amane Kanata
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
沙花叉クロヱ
Sakamata Chloe
風真いろは
Kazama Iroha
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
アイラニ・イオフィフティーン
Airani Iofifteen
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
小鳥遊キアラ
Takanashi Kiara
がうる・ぐら
Gawr Gura
七詩ムメイ
Nanashi Mumei
ハコス・ベールズ
Hakos Baelz
ないないない自分にじゃねて
Bye bye bye to my non-existent self
いってバイバイバイ
Saying bye bye bye
変わりちゃん　ほら変わりちゃん
Substitute-chan, look, substitute-chan
迷子じゃない　ごっこ遊びじゃない
I'm not lost, this isn't playing pretend
テンポないチャチャチャ　まあまあいいじゃん
No tempo, cha-cha-cha, it's alright
心配してトトト　やばいかも
Worried, tap-tap-tap, it might be bad
負けたくないから　燃えてきちゃうんだ　一歩踏み出すほど超不安
I don't want to lose, so I'm fired up; the more I step forward, the more anxious I get
追いつけ追い越せで未来へ　悩みながら走っていくんだ
Catch up and overtake towards the future, running while worrying
おっかなびっくりでのーのー
In fear and trembling, no-no
中途半端はしたくない
I don't want to do things halfway
だって現在(いま)をやっちゃってもう夢でスタートも
Because I'm doing the "now", even starting from a dream...
絶対的な理由で　ずっとずっとここにいるよ
For an absolute reason, I'll be here forever and ever
ないないない自分にじゃねて
Bye bye bye to my non-existent self
いってバイバイバイ
Saying bye bye bye
超えちゃう　ほら超えちゃう　お祭りじゃない　ごっこ遊びじゃない
I'll surpass it, see? It's not a festival, it's not playing pretend
絶対　好きな僕見つけようぜ
Definitely, let's find the "me" I like
Up & Down バタバタして　辛いときも
Up & down, flailing about, even in hard times
止まってなんかいられないでしょ　やるしかねー
We can't just stay stopped, can we? Gotta do it!
同じ気持ちに応えられるように　思ってることは閉じ込めたままで
To be able to respond to the same feelings, keeping my thoughts locked away
弱音は少しだけ残して　勝てる気しかしないぜOK？
Leaving just a few complaints behind, I only feel like I can win, OK?
言い訳なんてのーのー
Excuses are no-no
舞って踊っちゃうんじゃない？
Won't we just dance?
待って現在(いま)をやっちゃってもう無理って言えないよ
Wait, I'm doing the "now", I can't say it's impossible anymore
勝ちたい理由があるから　ずっとずっとここにあるよ
Because there's a reason to want to win, it'll always be here
ないないない自分にじゃねて
Bye bye bye to my non-existent self
いってバイバイバイ
Saying bye bye bye
超えちゃう　ほら超えちゃう　決まりじゃない　ごっこ遊びじゃない
I'll surpass it, see? It's not a rule, it's not playing pretend
絶対　好きな僕見つけようぜ
Definitely, let's find the "me" I like
Wow... yeah yeah
だって限界やんなっちゃっても　辞めてった時も
But even if I reached my limit and wanted to quit
勝ちたい理由が　負けない理由で　ずっとずっとここにいるよ
The reason I want to win is the reason I won't lose, and I'll be here forever
大嫌いな自分にチャオって言って　バイバイバイ
Say 'Ciao' to the self I hate, and bye-bye-bye
代われちゃう　ほら代われちゃう　ねぇ素敵じゃない？　ごっこ遊びじゃない
I can change, look, I can change. Isn't it wonderful? This isn't just playing house
限界やんなっちゃっても　無理って言えないよ
Even if I reach my limit, I can't say it's impossible
勝ちたい理由が　負けない理由が　ずっとずっとここにあるよ
The reason I want to win, the reason I won't lose, is right here forever
大嫌いな自分にチャオって言って　バイバイバイ
Say 'Ciao' to the self I hate, and bye-bye-bye
超えれちゃう　ほら超えれちゃう　ねぇ始まりじゃない？　ごっこ遊びじゃない
I can overcome it, look, I can overcome it. Isn't this a beginning? This isn't just playing house
代われちゃう　ほら代われちゃう　ねぇ素敵じゃない？　ごっこ遊びじゃない
I can change, look, I can change. Isn't it wonderful? This isn't just playing house
絶対　素敵な僕見つけようぜ
Let's definitely find a wonderful me
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？吸っちゃっていいの？
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Is it okay to suck your blood?
もう無理もう無理なんて　悪い子だね
Saying "No more, no more," you're such a bad kid
試したいな　いっぱいで吐きたいな
I want to try it. I want to drink until I'm full and vomit
まだ絶対いけるよ
You can still go on, definitely
最低最高ずっといききしてる
The absolute best and worst, I'm constantly going back and forth
甘くなる不安の果実
The fruit of anxiety that becomes sweet
脳を果てしない吐息をしても
Even if I exhale an endless sigh from my brain
いらないだけうるさいだけ
It's just unnecessary, just noisy
誰かと居れば　それはそれで
If I'm with someone, that's that
揺るがせた気持ちに　抗えない
I can't resist the feelings that were shaken
離れていても　感じてる変
Even if we're apart, I feel something's strange
溶け合った時間が　始めれるかも
The time we blended together might start running
今　この血も　切ないも
Now, this blood, and this sadness too
君のすべてを　食らうまで絶頂
Until I devour all of you—climax
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？吸っちゃっていいの？
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Is it okay to suck your blood?
もう無理もう無理なんて　悪い子だね
Saying "No more, no more," you're such a bad kid
試したいな　いっぱいで吐きたいな
I want to try it. I want to drink until I'm full and vomit
まだ絶対いけるよ
You can still go on, definitely
求めちゃってもがいたから
Because I sought it and struggled
手を振るように　始めまして
Like waving a hand, nice to meet you
愛嬌をください　まだ絶対いけるよ
Give me some charm. You can still go on, definitely
あたしヴァンパイア　まずはこっちおいで
I'm a vampire. First, come over here
内緒の想い　洗いざらい
All my secret thoughts, washed clean
吐き出したなら　まさに馬鹿に
If I've vomited them out, it's just foolish
誇り切れないけど　あまりじゃない
I can't be fully proud, but it's not too bad
そっと明日まで　待ってるの
Quietly waiting until tomorrow
繰り返す嫌だ　はぐらかした
Repeating "I hate it," I dodged the question
いつだってチャンスを　逃すのが
I'm always the one to miss the chance
止めどなき想い　叶えたいけど
Endless thoughts, I want them to come true, but
重なって押しつぶされちゃうのかも
Maybe they'll pile up and crush me
今　この血も　切ないも　君の
Now, this blood, and this sadness too... yours...
全て楽しくなっちゃう
Everything becomes fun
気持ちよくなっちゃう　溺れるまで
It starts to feel good, until I drown
癖になれるぜ絶頂
I can get addicted—climax
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？吸っちゃっていいの？
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Is it okay to suck your blood?
もう無理もう無理なんて　悪い子だね
Saying "No more, no more," you're such a bad kid
試したいな　いっぱいで吐きたいな
I want to try it. I want to drink until I'm full and vomit
まだ絶対いけるよ
You can still go on, definitely
死に物ヴァンパイア　いいの？吸っちゃっていいの？
Desperate vampire. Is it okay? Is it okay to suck your blood?
もう無理もう無理なんて　言わせても死に際
Even if I make you say "No more, no more," at the moment of death
絶対いけないほら絶対いけるよ
Definitely can't go—look, you definitely can
君の
Yours...
認めたくないから　せめて今宵目
Because I don't want to admit it, at least for tonight
足が見えるような　泡の中で
In the bubbles where feet are visible
愛嬌をください　まだ絶対いけるよ
Give me some charm. You can still go on, definitely
君のヴァンパイア　まずはこっちおいで
Your vampire. First, come over here
ちょっと背伸びなステップで　おっちょこちょわわわ
With a slightly grown-up step, being a bit clumsy-wawawa
みんなー！あにょー！
Everyone! Anyo!
ルーナ、参上！
Luna, here!
もう、何しにきたの？
Geez, what are you here for?
みんな！　新時代のルーナのステージ、
Everyone! Luna's new era stage,
一緒に盛り上げていくのらー！
Let's fire it up together-nora!
アイとかコイとか全部コトノハ
Love and romance are all just words
がっかりするだけ　ダメ押しするだけ
Only resulting in disappointment, only adding more bad news
あたしばかりダサい逆相乗
I'm the only one with this uncool reverse synergy
本当のところは　あなたに酔いたい
The truth is, I want to get drunk on you
失敗するのに　ビビってるだけ
I'm just scared of failing
格好なしの　きみしめの条件じゃん
It's an uncool, 'holding you tight' condition
こんな時どんな　顔すればいいか教えてほしいの
Tell me what kind of face I should make at a time like this
愛してるだとか　そんな言葉で壊れてみたいの
I want to try being broken by words like 'I love you'
困っちゃってイヤイヤ
I'm in a bind, no way, no way
決まんないの前髪が
My bangs just won't stay in place
怒っちゃってイヤイヤ
I'm getting mad, no way, no way
もっと可愛い子になっていたいのにな
I just want to become a cuter girl
あーあ！
Ahh!
ずっとサナギになって出直すわ
I'll turn back into a pupa and start over
何でもない言いたいこと言えたことない
It's nothing, I've never been able to say what I want
止めど止められないの
I can't stop it, I just can't
大人しくたってまた自己嫌悪
Even when I'm quiet, I'm full of self-loathing again
死にたいな ハイローサネオアワタシ
I want to die, high/low, sane or me
困っちゃってイヤイヤ
I'm in a bind, no way, no way
キマんないの前髪が
My bangs just won't stay in place
怒っちゃってイヤイヤ
I'm getting mad, no way, no way
羽が鳴って 灰になって 私まだ耐えたくないわ
Wings buzzing, turning to ash, I don't want to endure this yet
待って香水 飛び込んでみたいから
Wait, perfume, because I want to dive in
死にたいな ハイローサネオアワタシ
I want to die, high/low, sane or me
困っちゃってイヤイヤ
I'm in a bind, no way, no way
キマんないの前髪が
My bangs just won't stay in place
怒っちゃってどう？
I'm getting mad, how's that?
死にたいな 横前のシンデレラ
I want to die, the Cinderella in front of me
気になっちゃってほらほら
I'm getting curious, look, look
ハロー お疲れ様 あなたどう？
Hello, good job, how about you?
踊っちゃってフラフラ
Dancing around, feeling dizzy
もっと可愛い子になっていたいのにな
I just want to become a cuter girl
あーあ！
Ahh!
ちょっとおまじになってお日様
Casting a little spell, Mr. Sun
あーあ！
Ahh!
もっと仲良くなってそうじゃないの
Let's get closer, isn't that right?
あーあ！
Ahh!
ずっとサナギになって出直すわ
I'll turn back into a pupa and start over
剥がれ落ちたメイク スッピンのアニマル
Makeup peeling off, a bare-faced animal
見苦しくてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if it's unsightly, I'm gonna do it
お座りとかできない 待て待てもできない
I can't sit, I can't even stay
喉鳴らしていっちゃうまで
Until I'm purring away
さぐっとしようぜ 高まるビート
Let's do it quickly, the rising beat
良いも悪いも全然しよう
Let's do it all, good or bad
はまってみようか 突破するゲート
Shall we get hooked? Breaking through the gate
会いに行きたいわ 君だよ
I want to come see you, it's you
根掘り葉掘りほどに狂いたい
I want to go crazy enough to dig into everything
ところ構わずどうしちゃったの
What's happened, regardless of the place?
痛みすらもシェアしあえたら
If we could even share the pain
あたしは幸せです
Then I am happy
剥がれ落ちたメイク スッピンのアニマル
Makeup peeling off, a bare-faced animal
見苦しくてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if it's unsightly, I'm gonna do it
お座りとかできない 待て待てもできない
I can't sit, I can't even stay
喉鳴らしていっちゃうまで
Until I'm purring away
牙を出し叫べ ズキュンだ
Bare your fangs and scream, it's a "zukyun"
あたしは噛みついたら離さないニャ
Once I bite, I won't let go, nya
塗り重ねたメイク ばっちりのアニマル
Layers of makeup, a perfect animal
目を見開いて待ってるのよ
I'm waiting with my eyes wide open
あげさせちゃってよ 狂わさせちゃってよ
Let me give it, let me drive you crazy
惑わせちゃってよ
Let me lead you astray
あげさせちゃってよ 狂わさせちゃってよ
Let me give it, let me drive you crazy
惑わせちゃってよ
Let me lead you astray
まぁいなことなくてつまんない
It's boring with nothing special
せめてちょっと困ってほしかったな
I wish you were at least a little troubled
今日だけ特売れるなら
If I can be on special sale just for today
あたしは幸せになりたいです
I want to become happy
剥がれ落ちたメイク スッピンのアニマル
Makeup peeling off, a bare-faced animal
見苦しくてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if it's unsightly, I'm gonna do it
お座りとかできない 待て待てもできない
I can't sit, I can't even stay
喉鳴らしていっちゃうまで
Until I'm purring away
塗り重ねたメイク ばっちりのアニマル
Layers of makeup, a perfect animal
目を見開いて待ってるのよ
I'm waiting with my eyes wide open
お座りとかできない 待て待てもできない
I can't sit, I can't even stay
喉鳴らしていっちゃうまで
Until I'm purring away
牙を出し叫べ ズキュンだ
Bare your fangs and scream, it's a "zukyun"
あたしは噛みついたら離さないニャ
Once I bite, I won't let go, nya
塗り重ねたメイク ばっちりのアニマル
Layers of makeup, a perfect animal
目を見開いて待ってるのよ
I'm waiting with my eyes wide open
楽しんでるかー！
Are you having fun!
盛り上がってるかー！
Are you excited!
最後まで楽しんでいってねー！
Have fun until the very end!
というわけで...！
And so...!
一息ついちゃいましたけどもー！
We took a little breather, but...!
みなさーん！こんこよー！
Everyone! Konkoyo-!
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm Hakui Koyori, the brains of secret society holoX from Hololive 6th gen!
そして、うち、うち、うちだよー！
And, it's me, me, me!
大神ミオだよー！
It's Ookami Mio!
ちょっと何からいっていいか戸惑うやつですよ、それ。
That's a bit confusing to know what to say first.
もう、それはさておき、2人合わせて...
Well, setting that aside, the two of us together...
おここよーしーです！
Are Okokoyoshi!
はー、はー、踊りましたねー！
Phew, phew, we danced, didn't we!
踊りましたー。
We sure did.
はい！というわけで、ホロライブ 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
Yes! So, Hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
Day 2 holo*27ステージ、いよいよ始まったよー！
Day 2 holo*27 stage has finally begun!
いやー、本当に声いっぱい、ありがとう、幕張ー！
Wow, really, thanks for all the voices, Makuhari!
ありがとう！そしてコメントのみんなも見てるよね？
Thank you! And everyone in the comments is watching too, right?
見てるよー！配信ー！いぇーい！ありがとう！
We see you! The stream! Yay! Thank you!
いぇーい！みんなめっちゃ書いてくれてる！
Yay! Everyone is writing so much!
すごい！元気だねーって言われました。
Amazing! They said we're energetic.
元気かもー！元気だー！いぇーい！
Maybe we are! We're energetic! Yay!
あの、あのね、うち、あの、博衣、大神先輩のほうがしおらしいじゃないですか。
Um, you know, I... um, Hakui, Ookami-senpai is usually more demure, right?
うち、あの、はい、こうやって大きな舞台で、みんながこうやって声ワーって出してくれるの、初めてだから、
Me, um, yes, this is the first time in a big stage like this where everyone is shouting like "waah",
ちょっとどうしていいかわかんなくて。あ、どうしたらいいんだろう。
so I don't really know what to do. Oh, what should I do?
なるほど、そうなんですねー。俺なんか余裕そう...
I see, is that so. I look like I have plenty of room...
あ、実はこより、昨日も一回やってるんですよね。
Ah, actually, Koyori did this once yesterday too.
えー！そうなんですかー？そうなんですよー。
Eh! Is that so? It is.
え、じゃあ何かこう、いい感じの、あの、こう、みんなに投げかける言葉とか、
Eh, then could you teach me some nice words to throw at everyone,
教えてほしいんですけど、こより先輩！
Koyori-senpai!
あ、いいよ、いいよ、ミオくん。それは、「コール&レスポンス」ってやつだね！
Ah, sure, sure, Mio-kun. That's what we call "Call & Response"!
コール&レスポンス...！とは一体...！
Call & Response...! What on earth is that...!
説明しよう！コール&レスポンスとは、こっちがこうやって何かバーって投げかけたら、
Let me explain! Call & Response is, if we throw something out like this,
みんながワーってレスポンスしてくれるという、言葉の投げかけ合いのことなのであーる！
everyone responds back with a "waah"! It's an exchange of words!
なるほどー！やってみたーいっす、やってみたーいっす！じゃあちょっとやってみますか。
I see! I want to try it! Then, shall we try it a bit?
あの、我々ね、「アニマル」歌わせていただきましたけれども、
Um, we sang "Animal",
アニマルであの、カッコいいのと可愛いのと、結構ギャップをね、頑張ってやらせていただいたんですよね。
and we worked hard to show a gap between the cool parts and the cute parts.
すごいギャップある！ね、ギャップある！天元突破！天元突破！あ、天元突破したんですけど、
There's a huge gap! Right, a gap! Breaking the limits! We broke the limits, but...
みんなに、可愛いと思ったか、カッコいいと思ったか聞いてみましょう。
Let's ask everyone if they thought it was cute or cool.
いいですね、先輩それ！やってみよう、ミオくん。じゃあちょっとお手本見せるね。
That's good, senpai! Let's do it, Mio-kun. I'll show you an example first.
お願いします。じゃあ、アニマル、可愛いと思った人ー！
Please. Then, everyone who thought "Animal" was cute!
おー！いっぱいだ、ありがとう！じゃあ、やってみな、ミオくん。
Oh! So many, thank you! Now, you try it, Mio-kun.
あれ、ウェでもこんなに可愛いっていう人がいたら、もしかして、カッコいいって言ってくれる人がいなくて、
Wait, but if there are this many people saying it's cute, maybe there's no one who would say it's cool,
コール&レスポンスが成り立たない可能性...
and the call and response might not work...
確かに、そうかもしれません。ちょっと寂しい感じになるかもしれないけど、それも修行のうちだ、やってみな、ミオくん。
True, that might be the case. It might feel a bit lonely, but that's part of the training, give it a go, Mio-kun.
がんばります！アニマル、カッコいいと思った人ー！
I'll do my best! Everyone who thought "Animal" was cool!
おー！あれあれあれ？なんか同じぐらいの圧が...！きた、あれ？あれ？
Oh! Wait, wait, wait? There's about the same level of intensity...! It came, huh? Huh?
ということは、アニマルは可愛くてカッコいいということなんじゃないでしょうか。
Does that mean "Animal" is both cute and cool?
じゃあ、「かっこかわいい」と思った人って聞いたら、すごいことになっちゃいますかね？
Then, if we ask "everyone who thought it was cool-cute", will it be crazy?
もしかしたら幕張メッセが破裂してしまうかもしれません。
Makuhari Messe might even explode.
破裂しちゃうかも。このあとできなくなっちゃいますけど。ああ、大変だ。じゃあ聞いてみますか。
It might explode. We won't be able to continue after that. Oh, that's bad. Then, shall we ask?
せーの！アニマル、かっこかわいいと思った人ー！
One, two! Everyone who thought "Animal" was cool-cute!
うわー！割れるー！いぇーい！コメントもありがとう！ありがト！
Woaah! It's cracking! Yay! Thanks for the comments too! Thank you!
これがコール&レスポンスだよ、ミオくん。なるほど、めちゃくちゃ勉強になりました！
This is what call and response is, Mio-kun. I see, that was a great lesson!
さあ、もっとやってみようって言いたいところなんだけど、実は「時間」というものがあってだね、ミオくん。え、もしかしてもうおしまいなんですか？
Now, I'd love to say let's do more, but actually there's this thing called "time", Mio-kun. Eh, is it already over?
我々は、ここで締めないといけないんだ。えー！でもね、このライブはまだまだ続いていきますので！
We have to wrap it up here. Eh-! But, this live concert is still going on!
続いていくぞー！えい！ハッシュタグ #ホロニーナ をつけて、ぜひぜひスクショとかもいっぱい撮って呟いてください！
It's going to continue! Ei! Use the hashtag #HoloNina and please take lots of screenshots and tweet them!
いっぱいスクショ撮ってください！お願いします！いぇーい！
Take lots of screenshots please! Please do! Yay!
それでは我々も戻りますか！
Shall we head back as well?!
はい！行きますよ！せーの！
Yes! Let's go! Ready, set...
広がるホロライブ！
Hirugaru Hololive!
落ち込み携帯 どうしたって聞けば",
Depressed cell phone, whenever I ask what's wrong,
「何でもないよ」って言うんだ",
It says, "It's nothing."
そっかそっか 気のせいか",
I see, I see, just my imagination then?
で、それで引くものか",
And, like I'd just let it go at that.
本当に心配な強気",
Seriously worried about that bravado.
「やり過ぎはだめ」ってなんなら",
If anything, you say "Don't overdo it."
平気 平気 ありがとうね",
I'm fine, I'm fine, but thanks.
って、やっぱ普通じゃない",
But, that's definitely not normal.
あーまたまたまたまた全然強がんじゃん",
Ah, there you go again, acting all tough.
あたいに任せてね",
Leave it to me!
全部いっちゃいな",
Just let it all out.
だっていなんか苦しそうじゃん",
Because you look like you're in pain.
いっちゃいな",
Just let it out.
それもしんどいんだね了解",
So that's tough too, I get it.
笑えるようになるまで",
Until you can laugh again,
隣にいてあげて",
I'll stay by your side.
バカな冗談 言い合って",
Exchanging silly jokes...
覚悟しててね",
Get ready.
GENTSU PI PI PI
君がすり減らぬまで その元気を",
Until you're no longer worn out, this energy...
お裾分け 届けたい",
I want to share it with you.
いっぱいいっぱい うるさいぐらいに",
A whole lot, even to the point of being annoying.
追い込み携帯 気にしちゃって負けだ",
Being cornered by your phone, caring too much is a loss.
君が倒れちゃったら嫌だ",
I don't want you to collapse.
だって だって 不安じゃない",
Because, because, it's worrying.
って、これはわがままかな",
Or is this just me being selfish?
痛い 何がしたいだろう",
Ouch, what am I trying to do?
誰のためだろう",
Who is this for?
こうやって元気づけたり ブレーキ踏んだり",
Cheering you up like this, or stepping on the brakes.
もう馬鹿馬鹿 永遠自己嫌悪",
So stupid, endless self-loathing.
好きだ センチメンタル",
I love it, this sentimentality.
全部いっちゃいな",
Just let it all out.
だっていなんか苦しそうじゃん",
Because you look like you're in pain.
いっちゃいな",
Just let it out.
それもしんどいんだね了解",
So that's tough too, I get it.
君がすり減らすカウンターのスクランブル",
The scramble of counters you wear down.
そうだ 好きだなんて",
That's right, "I love you" or something...
絶対言えないよ",
I could never say that.
GENTSU PI PI PI
君も同じになりなよ 顔上げなよ",
You should be the same way, look up!
染まれ 一切合切 その想いに",
Let yourself be dyed, through and through, by those feelings.
やっぱり元気出させちゃう",
As expected, I'll make you feel better.
かといって無理は禁物じゃ",
But even so, overexertion is forbidden.
野菜 魚は食べましたかな",
Did you eat your vegetables and fish?
どっちどっちどっち",
Which one, which one, which one?
ちゃんと断れたい？ 怠慢な",
Want to refuse properly? How lazy.
でもちょっと気づいたよ 乙女な",
But I noticed a bit, your maidenly side.
慎重から臆病かな",
Is it being careful or just cowardly?
どっちどっちどっち",
Which one, which one, which one?
GENTSU PI PI PI
君も同じになりなよ 顔上げなよ",
You should be the same way, look up!
染まれ 一切合切 その想いに",
Let yourself be dyed, through and through, by those feelings.
いっちゃいな",
Just let it out.
だっていなんか苦しそうじゃん",
Because you look like you're in pain.
いっちゃいな",
Just let it out.
それもしんどいんだね了解",
So that's tough too, I get it.
笑えるようになるまで 隣にいてあげて",
Until you can laugh again, I'll stay by your side.
バカな冗談 言い合って",
Exchanging silly jokes...
覚悟しててね",
Get ready.
Rata-tata sweet appetite
Fearless and my makeup is done
Don't worry it's my kingdom
Look at me the face I wanted to be
A makeover indeed, am I your type do you like it darlin'?
Rata-tata sweet appetite
Come closer now it's complete
Do you hear my heartbeat?
So far so good, just set the mood right
But this is only going to drive me crazy
Are you embarrassed right now?
Pushing somehow
But I am guessing it is the same for you anyway
Look here don't blink
Tell me what you think
Do we both know the answer now, wouldn't you agree?
What should I do? I hope you don't find out
The things I'm shy about
What should I do? My head is still spinning
The rest is exploding
I'm only asking for another chance
Plan B I'll get closer this time
Next shot better be the bullseye
New appeal, a sweet and spicy reveal
My look talked the talk but now my heart is so naked help me
Rata-tata sweet appetite
I got to static-sign
Patience is just not for me
No we can't stop now, not for one second
'Cause this is only driving me to full-on panic!
I'm so embarrassed right now
I'm blushing somehow
But nothing that I seem to do ever bothers you
Looking in your eyes
Just want you to know that I really, really, really like you
Are you embarrassed right now?
I'm blushing somehow
But I am guessing it is the same for you and me
Look here don't blink
And tell me what you think
But we both know the answer now, wouldn't you agree?
What should I do?
I hope you don't find out the things I'm shy about
My head is still spinning, the words are big for me
What should I do?
I hope you don't find out the things I'm shy about
My head is still spinning, the words are big for me
I'm only asking for another chance
Oh pretty please, I promise one last chance
なんだったら 楽勝だ 全部忘れちゃえよ
If that's the case, it's a breeze, just forget it all
舞って這って揺らして
Dancing, crawling, and swaying
楽しんでるでござるかー！
Are you having a good time?!
皆さまも一緒に全力で盛り上げてくださいね！
Everyone, please go all out and get hyped up together!
別にいいじゃんか へこんだってOK
It doesn't really matter, it's okay to feel down
後悔へのマッサージです
It's a massage for your regrets
思い通りがお好みなら
If you prefer things to go your way
ちょっとだけしんどいかもな
It might be a little tough
さっさこらどっこいしょ 今勝ったもん勝ちっしょ
Sassa kora dokkoisho, it's all about winning in the moment
通るだけですごいな ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
It's amazing just passing through! High, High, High, High!
さっさこらどっこいしょ こんなんすぐにおいな
Sassa kora dokkoisho, come on quickly with this
それ違っちゃうじゃん
That's not right, is it?
上がっちゃって ステージ出していこう
Get hyped and let's go out on stage
さらば 不安を踏みつけて
Farewell, stepping over anxiety
ソー ワンモアステップ 踏み出していこう
So one more step, let's move forward
さらば バイバイ 才能飛んでいけ
Farewell, bye-bye, let talent fly away
いいとこ見せたいんだ
I want to show my good side
なんだったら 楽勝だ 全部忘れちゃえよ
If that's the case, it's a breeze, just forget it all
セイ！もっと僕になるんだ
Say! I'll become more like myself
間違ったら またいつか 好きじゃんもー
If I make a mistake, again someday... I love it already!
なんだったら 楽勝だ 全部忘れちゃえよ
If that's the case, it's a breeze, just forget it all
やる気でなくってのそのそムーブOK
It's okay to move slowly when you have no motivation
追い越し追い越されても大丈夫
It's okay to overtake or be overtaken
諦めないことがきっと大正解
Not giving up is surely the right answer
疲れたらちょい休みなよ セイ！
If you're tired, take a little break. Say!
不安になるのは君が君に期待してるの その証拠なんだな セイ！
Becoming anxious is proof that you're expecting something from yourself. Say!
怖くなるなら それは僕も一緒なんだよ 間違えてたい
If you're getting scared, I'm the same. I want to make mistakes.
回っちゃって 足鳴らしていこう
Let's spin around and stomp our feet
さらば バイバイ 才能引き寄せ
Farewell, bye-bye, attracting talent
ソー ワンモアステップ 飛び乗っていこう
So one more step, let's jump on
さらば バイバイ 笑うため セイ！
Farewell, bye-bye, in order to laugh. Say!
いいとこ見せたいんだ
I want to show my good side
なんだったら 楽勝だ 全部忘れちゃえよ
If that's the case, it's a breeze, just forget it all
セイ！ もっと僕になるんだ
Say! I'll become more like myself
間違ったら またいつか 好きじゃんもー
If I make a mistake, again someday... I love it already!
もう一歩
One more step
ほらもう一歩
Look, one more step
まだ終われない
It's not over yet
ここで終われない僕ら
We can't end here
失敗気にしなくったっていいんじゃない
Isn't it okay not to worry about failure?
上がっちゃって ステージ出していこう
Get hyped and let's go out on stage
さらば 不安を踏みつけて
Farewell, stepping over anxiety
ソー ワンモアステップ 踏み出していこう
So one more step, let's move forward
さらば バイバイ 才能飛んでいけ
Farewell, bye-bye, let talent fly away
回っちゃって 足鳴らしていこう
Let's spin around and stomp our feet
さらば バイバイ 才能引き寄せ
Farewell, bye-bye, attracting talent
ソー ワンモアステップ 飛び乗っていこう
So one more step, let's jump on
さらば バイバイ 笑うため セイ！
Farewell, bye-bye, in order to laugh. Say!
いいとこ見せたいんだ
I want to show my good side
なんだったら 楽勝だ 全部忘れちゃえよ
If that's the case, it's a breeze, just forget it all
セイ！ もっと僕になるんだ
Say! I'll become more like myself
間違ったら またいつか 好きじゃんもー
If I make a mistake, again someday... I love it already!
セイ！
Say!
いいとこ見せたいんだ
I want to show my good side
なんだったら 楽勝だ
If that's the case, it's a breeze
全部忘れちゃえよ
Just forget it all
もっと僕になるんだ
I'll become more like myself
間違ったら またいつか 好きじゃんもー
If I make a mistake, again someday... I love it already!
なんだったら 楽勝だ
If that's the case, it's a breeze
全部忘れちゃえよ
Just forget it all
皆殿、こんにちはでござるー！
Hello everyone, de gozaru~!
ホロライブ6期生、侍の風真いろはでござるー！
Hololive 6th generation, the samurai Kazama Iroha de gozaru~!
皆殿、でござるー！
Everyone, degozaru!
皆殿、やっと会えたねー！
Everyone, we finally meet!
わあ、すごいでござる！わあ、ツルツル！ありがとう！
Wow, it's amazing! Wow, so smooth! Thank you!
ちょっと、すごいいっぱい動いて、ちょっとヘトヘトなところもあるんですけども...
I've been moving around a lot, so I'm a bit exhausted, but...
風真の夢物語、どうでしたかー！？
How was Kazama's "Yumemonogatari"?!
わあ、すごい！ありがとうございます！
Wow, amazing! Thank you so much!
憧れのね、この大きなステージに立つことができました！
I was finally able to stand on this large stage I've longed for!
皆に会えて嬉しいでござるー！
I'm so happy to meet everyone, degozaru!
あ、どうしよう。ちょっと一人でのね、
Ah, what should I do. Since it's a solo...
MCということで、すごく緊張しているんですけど、
MC segment, I'm very nervous, but...
せっかく来たのでね、
since I'm here,
やっぱりやってみたいことが、風真、あるんですけど、
there's something I, Kazama, really want to try.
皆殿、付き合ってくれますかー！？
Everyone, will you join me?!
やったー！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
じゃあ皆ね、風真の決め台詞、
Well then everyone, you know Kazama's catchphrase,
わかってると思うんですけど、
I think you all know it, but...
「ノット・ほにゃらら、イエス・ほにゃらら」をね、
the "Not honyarara, Yes honyarara" one,
皆と一緒にやりたいなと思うので、風真の後に続いてください！
I'd like to do it with everyone, so please repeat after me!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
ノット・
Not...
ニンニン！
Nin-nin!
イエス・
Yes...
ジャキンジャキン！
Jakin-jakin!
でござるー！ありがとう！
degozaru! Thank you!
わーすごーい！本当にね、こんな大きいステージ立ってびっくりしてるんだけど、
Wow, amazing! Honestly, I'm surprised to be on such a big stage, but...
コメント欄の皆も見えてますよー！
I can see everyone in the comments section too!
見てるぞ、ジャキンジャキン、ニンニン、ありがとう！
I'm watching! Jakin-jakin, nin-nin, thank you!
ね、さっきミオ先輩と、フブちゃんがね、
Hey, earlier Mio-senpai and Fubu-chan...
どうやらコール＆レスポンスなるものをやってんで、風真もやってみたんですが、
it seems they did a "call and response," so I tried it too,
せっかく来たからね、
but since I'm here,
皆殿ともうちょっと遊んでいきたいななんて思っておりまして、
I'd like to play with everyone a little more,
皆、風真の色は何色ですかー！？
Everyone, what color is Kazama's color?
緑ー！
Green!
うわ、すごい！色が、色がついてる！
Wow, amazing! The colors, the colors are there!
じゃあその、ペンライトでウェーブやっていきたいと思います！
Then, I'd like to do a wave with those penlights!
じゃあこっちの方からいくよー！
I'll start from this side!
いきます、せーの！
Here we go, one, two...!
うわあああああああ！
Uwaaaaaaa!
え、すごい！素敵でござる！ありがとう！
Eh, amazing! That's wonderful, degozaru! Thank you!
はい、こっから先もホロ27ステージ、まだまだ続いていきます！
Yes, from here on, the holo*27 stage will still continue!
素敵な楽曲、そしてダンスがどんどん、どんどん続いていくので、
Wonderful songs and dances will keep coming one after another,
お楽しみに！そして何やらこっから先はまたちょっと違った世界観に、
so look forward to it! And it seems from here on, it'll be a slightly different worldview,
なると言うことで、ちょっと風真もどうなるかドキドキなんですが、
so I'm also a bit excited to see how it turns out,
一緒にこの後も楽しみましょうねー！
let's enjoy what's coming next together too!
あ、もっと本当はお喋りしたいけど、
Ah, I really want to talk more, but...
風真も次に行かなきゃ行けないんで、皆殿、
I have to head to the next part, so everyone,
締めの挨拶、分かってるでござるよなー！？
you know the closing greeting, right?!
あ、しまった！風真が一個大事なこと忘れてた！
Ah, oh no! I forgot one important thing!
ひひ、許して！
Hehe, forgive me!
YouTubeの皆殿ー！
Everyone on YouTube!
YouTubeでの皆殿のこちらの配信が無料パートここまでとなっております！
This stream for everyone on YouTube ends the free part here!
寂しい、寂しいけど、
It's sad, it's sad, but...
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたい皆殿は、
everyone who still wants to get hyped together,
概要欄から、ここ？ここ？ここ？
please check the description, here? here? here?
是非ね、配信サイトへチケット買って見に来てくださいねー！
be sure to buy a ticket on the streaming site and come watch!
というわけで、今度こそ、締めのご挨拶しますよ！
So, this time for sure, I'll do the closing greeting!
皆殿、決め台詞の準備はいいでござるかー！？
Everyone, are you ready for the catchphrase?!
それでは、
And now,
せーの、
One, two,
ひろがれ！ホロライブー！
Expand! Hololive!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free segment has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!